nexoneu.com 2013-12-10

# NEXON Europe - Play fun Online Games : Legal > PrivacyPolicy

This agreement contains important legal information.

 **YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS – NEXON EUROPE PRIVACY POLICY**

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about our privacy practices and your privacy rights. Because the success of our Services is dependent on building and maintaining goodwill with our users, we are committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our Site and Services. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect; how we collect, use, and share the information; your choices related to our information practices; and how we protect your information.

Some terms used herein are defined in the last paragraph of the Privacy Policy. Please refer below for definitions. This Privacy Policy is governed by and incorporated by reference into the Terms available on the following website [<http://en.nexoneu.com/NXEU.aspx?PART=/Legal/TermsOfUse>], and should be interpreted consistent therewith.

You may be able to access third party services (including through links, advertisements, or other means), including co-branded or other affiliated websites which are not owned or operated by us, from our Site or Services. When doing so, please understand that those third parties have their own set of privacy and information practices. We strongly recommend that you read their privacy policies and terms and conditions of use to understand how they collect, use, and share information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on the websites of third parties. 

**Table of Contents**

**1\. Information Practices Concerning Children**

**2\. Types of Information We Collect**

**3\. How We Collect Information About You**

**4\. How We Use the Information We Collect**

**5\. Who Collects Your Information**

**6\. Sharing of Your Information**

**7\. Your Choices**

**8\. Security of Your Information**

**9\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

**10\. Contact Us**

**11\. Definitions**

**1\. Information Practices Concerning Children**

Our Services and Site are not directed to children under the age of 14 and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If you are under the age of 14, please stop using our Services and Site unless your legal guardian has given their consent to use our Services and Site. It is our policy not to knowingly solicit or permit children under the age of 14 to provide their information for any purpose.

We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in monitoring their children’s use of our Services and Site. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently collected information from children under the age of 14, we will make efforts to promptly delete the information. 

**2\. Types of** **Information We Collect**

**You consent to us collecting the following information:**

· **_Information We Collect About You_**. 

When you use our Services, we may collect and store information that you have directly provided on a voluntary basis. The collection and/or storage of information about you will usually take place in the context of either (1) the purchase of items or services through our on-line stores, (2) product or account registration, or registration for on-line game participation, (3) player match-up services, (4) message boards or forums, (5) contest registrations, (6) a consumer complaint, (7) surveys, (8) customer service and/or (9) the sign-up for newsletters. Information collected about you may include your name, date of birth, email address, phone number, physical address, any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual. We do not require all the above listed information from you in order to access our Sites. However, you will not be able to utilize certain products, services, or features that require registration or receive materials such as newsletters unless such related information is provided to us. Visitors purchasing products or services will be required to provide additional information such as a valid credit card number, expiration date, and shipping and billing addresses.Once registered, we may ask you to complete a NEXON user profile. Your user profile may include your username, profile picture, password and/or other information such as your age, gender, and/or game and platform preferences.

· **_Technical and Usage Information._ **When you use our Services, we collect technical and usage information such as your IP address, your browser type, browser language and signature, referring and exit URLs, interactions with other users, usage statistics with the Services, and device identification information regarding the computers, the servers or other devices with which you use our Services. For more information on how we utilize IP addresses and cookies, please see Section 3, “How We Collect Information about You.”

· **_Information communicated or shared by users._** Even if we have no obligation whatsoever to monitor the Services and/or the Site and would in any event only do so occasionally. We are entitled to collect and store information about your actions if we would suspect, on the basis of objective elements, that your actions on the Site or with respect to the Services, including communications on forums, private communications or images of in-game situations, could infringe the Terms, violate NEXON's rights or property (and endanger amongst others the integrity and the security of the Services and the Site), endanger your safety or the safety of other users or otherwise be illegal. 

**3.How We Collect Information About You**

We may collect information about you, your device, and your usage in a number of ways:

· _When Provided Directly from You_. As mentioned above, we collect information about you directly from you, including when you register with us or if you send an e-mail to us through our Site.

· _When Communicated or Shared with Other Users_. You may also participate in certain activities on our Services that give you the opportunity to voluntarily communicate or share information with other NEXON users, such as posting messages on a message board, in-game situations, posting public comments to user profiles or games, sending private messages, sending invitations, and posting photos. We may occasionally monitor, record and store these communications in order to protect your safety or the safety of other users, to assist with regulatory or law enforcement efforts, or to protect and defend NEXON’s rights and property. You consent to the recording, storage and disclosure of such communications you send or receive for these purposes. You agree that the recording of this information can be made possible via software that may be installed when you download software to use the Service.

· _Through IP Addresses and cookies_. When you use the Service, we may collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the Service you visit, the order in which you visit them and which hyperlinks you "click." Collecting such information involves logging your IP address (i.e., the unique number assigned to your server or Internet Service Provider ("ISP")), operating system specifications and browser software used to access the Service. Although such information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from an IP address your ISP and the geographic location of your point of connectivity. 

We also use "cookies" that is, small text files placed on your computer's hard drive. In practical terms, cookies are used by an origin website to send state information to a user's browser and to return information about the user's browsing behaviour to the origin site your identification card for the computers, or servers that placed them there. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. We use cookies on the Site to allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently certain pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of the Site. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. By adhering to the present Privacy policy you accept the use of cookies, without prejudice to your right to refuse afterwards such a use. You are able to control how and to choose whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser software. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your web browser software.

**4.How We Use the Information We Collect**

We may use the information we collect in the following ways:

· To create your account, which allows you to play our games and communicate with other NEXON users; 

· To provide you the proper functioning of the Service which may require the sharing of information with third party(ies) as set forth below in article 6.;

· To provide you with a customized or personalized experience;

· To provide you with technical support or to respond to your questions or comments;

· For legal purposes, for example to enforce our Terms or to prevent fraud or other illegal activities;

· To provide you with relevant and targeted advertising from NEXON or third parties; 

· To send you e-mails with useful updates, events, information or promotions about our Services or other products and services.

**5\. Who Collects Your Information**

When you are asked for information while using the Site or Service, you are sharing that information with NEXON, its parent, its sister companies, and its affiliates, unless specifically stated otherwise. As a result of this sharing, you may receive communications from any of NEXON’s affiliates. In addition, some services are provided in conjunction with partner companies, and thus the information about you may be collected by another company other than NEXON. However, in such instance you will be notified at the time the information is collected. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of information by not using that particular service or by not providing any information at that time. 

Please be aware that we cannot control the activities of third parties to whom we provide data, and as such we cannot guarantee that they adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as NEXON.

**6.Sharing of Your Information**

It is our policy not to share the information about you with third parties except with the following parties or in the following circumstances. We may share anonymous or anonymised information with third parties for various purposes, including for the purpose of explaining our user demographics or improving the quality or delivery of our Services and the marketing materials available through our Services. Although we will not share the information about you with third parties for the purpose of enabling third parties to send marketing materials to you about their products or the products of others, we may use third party advertisers to deliver advertising within the NEXON Servicing environment. 

If you do not want us to share the information about you with the third parties set forth below for particular purposes as described, please see Section 7 below, Your Choices, or do not provide us any information about you or use our Services. 

**· _Third Party Service Providers._ **We may use third party service providers, such as payment gateway companies, platform service companies, and analytics companies, to help us provide or improve the Services we offer you. We may share information about you with these third party service providers so that they may provide their services to us in order to allow a proper functioning of the Service. Some of these third party service providers are located in the Republic of Korea (Korea), outside the territories of the European Union (EU)/European Economic Area (EEA), which may not provide the same adequate protection for personal data as the EU. ****

**· _Other NEXON Users._ Some of the information about you (included in your profile and nicknames) **may also be visible to other NEXON **users through the use of the Site, Services or through other related websites**. Other NEXON users may be able to view information about your uses and interactions, such as your game results, scores, and profile information. ****

**· _Legal Purposes._ **We may provide information about you to third parties where we have a good faith belief that doing so is required by law or to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities. We may also provide your information to third parties in order to protect the rights or property of a third party or NEXON, including for the purposes of enforcing our Terms. ****

**· _Health or Safety_. **We may share the information about you when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the health or safety of you, another person, or the public generally. ****

· **_Sale or Merger._ **If NEXON is involved in a major business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of its assets, we may transfer the information about you to the successor organization in such transition. If material changes to NEXON’s privacy practices will occur as a result of the business transition, we will amend the Privacy Policy and the Information you previously submitted will continue to be treated pursuant to the last version of the Privacy Policy you agreed to unless you continue to use the Applications, which usage shall constitute consent to the new practices. The amended Privacy Policy will be notified on the Site and we will also notify you per email.

· **_Game Events._** For some game related events, we may share information, including your profile and nicknames, with third parties and either NEXON or the third party will post relevant privacy information in the official rules and/or registration area for the game related events. Should that privacy information, conflict with this Privacy Policy, the privacy policy of that particular game event will govern. 

· **_Licensors and Developers_** _._ We may share your Information with our partner licensors and developers during and upon termination of the contracted service in case the license agreement with the partner licensors and developers requires as such. The licensors and developers may be located outside the territories of the EU/EEA, and more particularly in Korea and in the U.S., which may not provide the same adequate protection for personal data as the EU. Partner licensors and developers in principle respect the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the EEA. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>. 

**7.Your Choices**

You may at any time indicate that you wish us to stop processing the information about you (if such information is necessary for you to have an account, you will no longer be able to use the Game and may no longer be able to use other aspects of the Service). 

You may also at any time "opt out" of receiving materials described in this Privacy Policy from us and/or our affiliates, advertisers or other business partners. The materials that we send you (e.g., e-mails) will indicate that such materials are from us and will always provide you with a method of "opting out" of receiving future materials of a similar nature. If you do not "opt out" of receiving such materials, this will signify your continuing consent to NEXON using your information to continue to provide you with such materials and otherwise share the information about you with or transferring it to our affiliates, advertisers or other business partners who provide products or services (or advertisements, marketing materials or other information) that we believe may be of interest to you. 

However, we will not release your credit card information to third parties without your consent unless necessary to complete a transaction between you and such third party. If you decide that you would like to "opt-out" of receiving such materials from NEXON, please edit your account information on our Site accordingly. If, at any time after you have provided us with such information, you decide that you would like to "opt-out" of NEXON providing it to its affiliates, advertisers or other business partners, please contact our customer service department by using the E-mail of Inquiry form on the Site (at: http://www.nexoneu.com). Keep in mind that, while NEXON encourages its affiliates, advertisers and business partners to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our users and otherwise to handle the information about you in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from us or independently. NEXON reserves the right to contact you at any time using the information about you for administrative or billing-related issues. 

**8.Security of Your Information**

Although we do not represent that we follow any particular, independent code of best practices, we maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your information. For example, we protect some of your information by using a firewall and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security threats, there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, so we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We strongly recommend that you take steps to maximize the security of your information, such as not sharing your login information and logging out of your account after you are done using our Service.

We store your information in the EU/EEA as well as in other territories. You consent to such storage and to the transfer of information from one territory to another, even when these territories do not provide for the same adequate personal data protection than the EU/EEA.

We will take reasonable steps to require any third parties who you authorize us to share information about you with to comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**9.Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we amend this Privacy Policy, we will notify you and other users by posting and/or e-mail to the address which you have provided while registering to the Services, a revised version of the Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will take effect after a reasonable time span as set forth in the notice of such changes. We will provide the notice by posting on the Site. Your continued use of the Site or Service after such notice and an appropriate time span as set forth in the notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. We recommend that you return to the Site periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this Privacy policy.

**10.Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our information practices generally, you can submit a ticket to us through the Site available on [<http://support.nexoneu.com/Main/Default.aspx>]. We allow you to access and, if necessary to be compliant with data protection law and in particular to change incorrect personal data, change or modify the information about you. For information that you have provided to us, you may do so by accessing and modifying your information through the Site. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes or modifications. Unfortunately, we cannot always ensure that such changes or modifications will be reflected in all iterations of your information as previously stored.

**11\. Definitions.**

“Services” à Services shall collectively mean the website at http://www.nexoneu.com or such url as may replace it from time to time (the "Site"), and all Site-related online products, online services proved by NEXON Europe S.à r.l., a company incorporated under the laws of the Grand-Duchy of Luxembourg and with registered office at 7 Rue Guillaume Kroll, L-1882 Luxembourg, its affiliated companies (collectively, "NEXON", "we" or "us" (and "our" shall be construed accordingly)).

“Including” à “Include,” “Includes,” “Including,” “include,” “includes,” and “including” herein mean including without limitation.

“Post” à To upload, post, create, make available, send, share, communicate or transmit.

“Privacy Policy” à This policy available at **[**<http://en.nexoneu.com/NXEU.aspx?PART=/Legal/PrivacyPolicy>].

“Terms” à The terms and conditions, available at [<http://en.nexoneu.com/NXEU.aspx?PART=/Legal/TermsOfUse>], including the Privacy Policy, available at [<http://en.nexoneu.com/NXEU.aspx?PART=/Legal/PrivacyPolicy>]. 

Effective Date [or Last Updated]: 8 of May 2013
